### Hello! I am

# Muh Syaiful Adli

Web Developer



### **ABOUT ME**

I am a hard worker and a persistent learner. 3 years experience in website development at PT Tripedia Global Adventura and Yayasan Satu Karsa Karya. Always want to develop and learn the latest programming languages. Have good communication, analysis and problem solving skills.



# PERSONAL INFORMATION

+62853-2525-5626

syaiful.adly2@gmail.com

Kabupaten Sukoharjo, Provinsi Jawa Tengah, 57552

Age: 27

# **FORMAL EDUCATION**

2010 - 2013 SMA Negeri 4 Surakarta

2013 - 2018 Ilmu dan Teknologi Pangan Universitas Sebelas Maret Surakarta, GPA = 3.50

## NON FORMAL EDUCATION

2021 HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL Course by Progate

2022 UI/UX Design Mastery Course by Skilvul

2022 React Developer Course by Teknoblox

### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2020 Part-Time Teacher at Neo Evolution

Staff of Pengelolaan Data dan

2020 - 2021 informasi Division at Yayasan Satu

Karsa Karya

2022 - 2023 Front End Developer at PT. Tripedia

Global Adventura

# **ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE**

2015 Head of Kaderisasi Division at Kelompok Studi Ilmiah

2016 Head of Media Informasi Division at Kelompok Studi Ilmiah

# **Skills**

Here are some programming skills that I have learned.

Codelgniter	Laravel	
(js)		
Express Js	React Js	
V	MySQL	
Vue Js	MySQL	
•	~	
MongoDB	Tailwind	
В		
BootStrap	Flutter	